Woman's Building
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Woman's Building records
1970-1992
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Woman's Building
33.4 linear feet
The records of the Woman's Building feminist arts organization in Los Angeles measure 33.4 linear feet and date from 1970-1992. Originally founded by artist Judy Chicago, graphic designer Sheila Levant de Bretteville, and art historian Arlene Raven in 1973, the Woman's Building served as an education center and public gallery space for women artists in southern California. The records document both the educational and exhibition activities and consist of administrative records, financial and legal records, publications, curriculum files, exhibition files, grant funding records and artist's works of arts and prints. A significant portion of the collection documents the Women's Graphic Center, a typesetting, design, and printing service operated by The Woman's Building.
Provenance
The Woman's Building records were donated to the Archives of American Art in 1991 by Sandra Golvin, President of the Board of Directors.
Separated Material
The Archives of American Art donated 5 boxes of video tape from the collection to the Long Beach Museum of Art, Video Annex in 1994. According to documentation, this was the desire of Sandra Golvin and the Board of Directors of the Woman's Building.
Related Material
Among the other resources relating to the Woman's Building in the Archives of American Art is an oral history with Suzanne Lacy on March 16, 1990, March 24, 1990, and September 24, 1990. While not credited as a founding member, Lacy was among the first group of staff of the Woman's Building which she discusses in her interview.
Restrictions on Access
The collection is open for research. Use requires an appointment.
Historical Note
In 1973, artist Judy Chicago, graphic designer Sheila Levant de Bretteville, and art historian Arlene Raven founded the Feminist Studio Workshop (FSW), one of the first independent schools for women artists. The founders established the workshop as a non-profit alternative education center committed to developing art based on women's experiences. The FSW focused not only on the development of art skills, but also on the development of women's experiences and the incorporation of those experiences into their artwork. Central to this vision was the idea that art should not be separated from other activities related to the developing women's movement. In November of 1973 the founders rented workshop space in a vacated building in downtown Los Angeles and called it The Woman's Building, taking the name from the structure created for the 1893 World's Columbian Exposition in Chicago. The FSW shared space with other organizations and enterprises including several performance groups, Womanspace Gallery, Sisterhood Bookstore, the National Organization of Women, and the Women's Liberation Union.
When the building they were renting was sold in 1975, the FSW and a few other tenants moved to a three-story brick structure, originally designed to be the administrative offices of the Standard Oil Company in the 1920s. In the 1940s, it had been converted into a warehouse and consisted of three floors of open space, conducive to publically available extension classes and exhibitions offered by the Woman's Building staff and students. By 1977, the majority of the outside tenants had left the Woman's Building, primarily because they were unable to sustain business in the new location. The new building was more expensive to maintain and the FSW staff decided to hire an administrator and to create a board structure to assume the financial, legal, and administrative responsibility for the Building. The funds to operate came from FSW tuition, memberships, fund-raising events, and grant monies.
In 1981, the Feminist Studio Workshop closed, as the demand for alternative education diminished. The education programs of the Building were restructured to better accommodate the needs of working women. The Woman's Building also began to generate its own artistic programming with outside artists, including visual arts exhibits, performance art, readings, and video productions. That same year, the Woman's Building founded the Women's Graphic Center Typesetting and Design, a profit-making enterprises designed to strengthen its financial base. Income generated from the phototypesetting, design, production, and printing services was used to support the educational and art making activities of the Building.
When the graphics business closed in 1988, the Woman's Building suffered a financial crisis from which it never fully recovered. The Building closed its gallery and performance space in 1991.
Scope and Content Note
The records of the Woman's Building measure 33.4 linear feet and date from 1970 to 1992. The organization played a key role as an alternative space for women artists energized by the feminist movement in the 1970s. The records document the ways in which feminist theory shaped the Building's founding core mission and goals. During its eighteen year history, the Building served as an education center and a public gallery space for women artists in Los Angeles and southern California; the records reflect both functions of the Building's activities.
The Administrative Files series documents the daily operations of the Building, with particular emphasis on management policies, budget planning, history, cooperative relationships with outside art organizations and galleries, special building-wide programs, and relocation planning. Included in this series are the complete minutes from most Building committees from 1974 through closing, including the Board of Directors and the Advisory Council. The General Publicity and Outreach series is particularly complete, containing publicity notices from most events, exhibits, and programs held at the Woman's Building, including brochures, announcements, programs, invitations, press releases, newspaper clippings, and magazine articles.
The Woman's Building's educational programs centered on courses offered by the Feminist Studio Workshop and the Extension Program. While the Workshop provided a two-year program for women interested in fully developing their artistic talent, the Extension Program offered a broad range of classes, specifically oriented to working women interested in art and art vocations. The records fully document both programs, focusing on the course development and descriptions, teacher contracts, class evaluations, budget planning, and scholarship programs. Although the Archives does not have the entire slide library, there are files concerning the establishment and administration of the library, as well as a few folders of slides.
The Gallery Programs series houses the records of the visual, performing, literary and video arts events held at the Woman's Building. Administrative files detail the daily operation of the gallery spaces. The files in the remaining subseries are primarily arranged by event and contain proposals, announcements, publicity, and artist biographies.
The Women's Graphic Center became a profit-making arm of the Woman's Building in 1981 but the typesetting and design equipment had been used by staff and students since 1975. The records in this series focus on the work produced at the Center, including general projects and artist designs and art prints. Many of the design and printing examples were produced for Woman's Building events and programs. Art work not designated as Center projects can be found in the Artist's Works of Art series.
The Printed Materials series contains relevant feminist and art publications not produced by or for the Woman's Building.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed in the online catalog of the Archives of American Art under the following index terms:
Subjects:
Chicago, Judy, 1939-; Raven, Arlene; de Bretteville, Sheila Levant; Women's Graphic Center (Los Angeles, Calif.); Feminist Studio Workshop
Subjects-Topical:
Art -- Study and teaching -- California -- Los Angeles; Feminism and art; Art galleries, Commercial -- California -- Los Angeles; Women artists -- California
Types of Materials:
Artists' books; Works of art; Slides
Names:
Chicago, Judy, 1939-; Raven, Arlene; de Bretteville, Sheila Levant
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into 7 series.
Series 1: Administrative Files, circa 1970-1991 (Box 1-9; 9 linear feet)
Series 2: Educational Programs, 1971-1991 (Box 10-14; 4.9 linear feet)
Series 3: Gallery Programs, 1973-1991 (Box 14-20; 5.6 linear feet)
Series 4: Women's Graphic Center, circa 1976-1989 (Box 20-23; 32-50 5.6 linear feet)
Series 5: Artists' Works of Art, circa 1972-1990 (Box 24-25; 51-53 1.7 linear feet)
Series 6: Grants, 1974-1992 (Box 25-30; 5.3 linear feet)
Series 7: Printed Materials (Not Woman's Building), 1970-1983 (Box 30-31; 1.3 linear feet)
Series Descriptions/Container Listing
- Administrative Files, circa 1970-1991, Series 1:; (Box 1-9; 9 linear ft.)
  The files within this series document the daily administration of the Women's Building, including financial, fundraising, outreach, and publication functions. This series also documents the Board of Directors' relationship with the Building staff and activities. The files are arranged alphabetically within each subseries.
  The Administrative Files are arranged into five subseries:
  1.1: Alphabetical Files, circa 1970-1991
  1.2: Board of Directors, 1973-1991
  1.3: Building Publications, 1973-1990
  1.4: Publicity and Outreach, 1973-1991
  1.5: Fundraising and Outreach, 1974-1990
  - Alphabetical Files, circa 1970-1991, 1.1:
    - Activities, 1973-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Notebook, Part 1, circa 1979, (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
    - Advertising, circa 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Advocacy, Women in the Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Affirmative Action Policy, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Anniversary, Fifth - Planning and Publicity, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Anniversary, Fifth - Press Kit, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Anniversary, Fifteenth, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Anniversary, Fifteenth - Printed Materials, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Anniversary, Fifteenth - Video, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Anniversary, Fifteenth - Congratulation Letters1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Anniversary, Tenth - The First Decade, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Anniversary, Tenth - Drafts of The First Decade, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Ariadne: A Social Network, circa 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Archives, Jeanne Sison Project, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Archives, Negotiations with Archives of American Art, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Armory Center for the Arts, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Articles of Incorporation and Bylaws, Feminist Studio Workshop, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Articles of Incorporation and Bylaws, Woman's Building, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Articles of Incorporation, Certificate Amendment, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Association for Humanistic Psychology, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Brainstorming Planning Event, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Budgets, Budget Planning, circa 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Budgets, Budget Planning, 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Budgets, Budget Planning for Women's Graphic Center, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Budgets, Building Artists and Tenants, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Budgets, Event Planning, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Budgets, Financial Statements, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Budgets, Financial Statements, 1981-1990 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Budget, Programs, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Budgets, A Study of Financial Management by The Center for Nonprofit Management, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Budgets, Tax Exempt Returns, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Building Inspections, circa 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Bylaws, circa 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Calendar, 1989, September-October (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Calendar, 1989, November-December (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Calendar, 1990, March-April (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Calendar, 1990, May-June (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Calendar, 1990, July-August (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Calendar, 1990, September-October (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Calendar, Feminist Studio Workshop, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - California Confederation of the Arts, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - California Confederation of the Arts, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - California Confederation of the Arts, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Chicago 1893, Women's Exhibit at the Woman's Building, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Childcare at the Woman's Building, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Chilean Women's Delegation, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Chrysalis, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Collaboration with Museum of Contemporary Arts, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Conflict of Interest Policy, circa 1986 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Consultant Requests, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Contracts, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Contracts, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Contracts, Rental and Video, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence, 1974, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Maurine Renville, December 1979 - December, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1980, January-July (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1980, August-December (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1981, January-March (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1981, April-May (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1981, June (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1981, July-December (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Corrrespondence, 1986, January-July (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1986, August-December (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1987, January-April (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1987, May-July (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Corrrespondence, 1987, August-December (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1988, January-May (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1988, June-August (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1988, September-December (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1989, January-May (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1989, June-August (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1989, September-December (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Corrrespondence, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, Artists, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Cover Letter Templates, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - A Day in the Park, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Downtown Arts Partnership, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Executive Director Search, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Feminist Art Program in Fresno, circa 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Feminist Education at the Feminist Studio Workshop, The Woman's Building in Los Angeles by Ruth Iskin, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Fiscal Receivers, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Gallery Store, INANA, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Gallery Store Inventory, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Gallery Store Inventory, 1985-1989, (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 34-35)
    - History of the Woman's Building, circa 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Internship Program, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Job Responsibilities, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Kort and Adler Report, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Lease for North Spring Street Property, 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Legal Affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Letters of Support for Woman's Building Programs, 1984-1989 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Los Angeles Visual Arts (LAVA), circa 1982 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Los Angeles Artists Organizations (LAAO), circa 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Management Council Minutes, November 1, 1979 - April 30, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Management Council Minutes, 1980, May-July (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Management Council Minutes, 1980, August-December (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Management Council Minutes, 1981, January-April (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Management Council Minutes, 1981, May-August (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Management Council Minutes, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Marketing Plan, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Men's Committee, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Mission Statement, circa 1975-1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Mission and Goals, circa 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Multicultural Arts, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - National Association of Artists' Organizations, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - National Conference on Women and the Arts, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - National Organization for Women (NOW), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Notes from Pauli DeWitt, Exective Director, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Observations on the Woman's Building, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Organizational Chart, circa 1981-1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Quotes about the Woman's Building, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Personnel Handbook, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Policy and Procedures, Forms, circa 1981-1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Policy and Procedures, General Manual, 1980-1981, (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 21-24)
    - Policy and Procedures, How to Write a Memo, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Policy and Procedures, Locking the Building, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Policy and Procedures, Performance Information, circa 1981-1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Policy and Procedures, Space Rental, circa 1981-1990 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Program Evaluations, circa 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Programs, General Schedules, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Relocation, Board Members' Program, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Relocation, Neptune and Preeman Buildings, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Relocation, Space Needs, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Relocation, Van Nuys Annex, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Relocation, Van Nuys Annex Floor Plans, Building Permits, Slides, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Relocation, Van Nuys Annex NEA Application, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Renovation Expenses, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Reorganization Ideas, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Reorganization Ideas, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Sidell-Selick Dissertation on Woman's Building, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Southern California Committee for Contemporary Art Documentation, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Southern California Committee for Contemporary Art Documentation, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Southern California Committee for Contemporary Art Documentation, Slides and Stuff Subcommittee, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Southern California Committee for Contemporary Art Documentation, Slides and Stuff Subcommittee, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Speeches and Papers by Woman's Building Founding Mothers, circa 1970 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Speakers Bureau, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Staff Member Notebook, circa 1989 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Staff Meeting Notes, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Staff Memos, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Staff Memos, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Staff Memos, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Staff Memos, 1985-1989 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Staff Orientation Handbook, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Staff Program Reports, circa 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Staff, Vision and Planning Meeting, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Survey Returns, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Survey Returns, 1986-1987, (6 folders) (Box 4, Folder 5-10)
    - Thesis on the Woman's Building, Art Education and Art Making from a Feminist Perspective, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - TOSCO Report, circa 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Transcript of Dialogue Among Arlene Raven, Linda Burnham, Barbara Smith, and Cheri Gaulke, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Wattles Mansion Proposal, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - The Woman's Building: What is It? What Does It Have to Offer? by Jennie Gardner, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Womanspace, circa 1974 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Women's Art Tour of Chicago, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Women's Equity Day, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Writings by Sheila de Bretteville, circa 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Certificates from the City of Los Angeles1984, 1988 (Box 32 (sol))
  - Board of Directors, 1974-1991, 1.2:
    The Board of Directors files are arranged into four subsubseries:
    1.2.1: Minutes, 1974-1991
    1.2:2: Membership Files, 1978-1991
    1.2:3: Committees, 1977-1991
    1.2.4: Advisory Council, 1979-1989
    - Minutes, 1974-1991, 1.2.1:
      - Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Minutes, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Minutes, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Minutes, 1980, January-July (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Minutes, 1980, August-December (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Minutes, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Minutes, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Minutes, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Minutes, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Minutes, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - Minutes, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - Minutes, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - Minutes, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Membership Files, 1978-1991, 1.2.2:
      - Board Orientation Packet, circa 1981 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Membership Biographies and Applications - A-C, circa 1980-1989 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Membership Biographies and Applications - D-J, circa 1980-1989 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - Membership Biographies and Applications - K-R, circa 1980-1989 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Membership Biographies and Applications - S-Y, circa 1980-1989 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Membership Roster, 1984-1990 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - Orientation Packet, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Committees, 1977-1991, 1.2.3:
      - Development Committee Minutes, 1984-1989 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Development Committee, 1987-1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Finance Committee Minutes, 1978-1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Finance Committee, 1978-1981, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Fundraising Committee Minutes, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Gallery Committee Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Gallery Committee Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Gallery Committee Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Gallery Committee, circa 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Gallery Committee, circa 1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Gallery Committee, circa 1989 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Gallery Committee, circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Media Task Force Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Media Task Force Minutes, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Media Task Force Minutes, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Media Task Force, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Media Task Force, Artist's Proposals, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Move Committee Minutes, 1979, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Nominating Committee Minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Performance Committee Minutes, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Performance Committee, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Performance Committee, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Personnel Committee Minutes, circa 1981 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Planning Committee Minutes, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Program Committee Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Program Committee Minutes, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Program Committee Minutes, 1981-1982, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Program Committee Minutes, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Program Committee Minutes, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 29)